Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Case Number 409 Hearing Meeting, 1975, March 27 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Joint National Special Committee Meeting, 1975, April 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1975, June 9 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Cases Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Cases Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1975, June 10-11 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, June 10-11 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, September 22-25 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, September 22-25 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1975, September 23 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, September 23-24 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, September 23-24 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1975, September 23-24 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1975, September 23-24 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1975, September 23-24 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1975, December 15 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1975, December 16-17 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1975, December 16-17 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, April 20-21 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, April 20-21 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1976, April 20-21 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, April 20-21 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, April 20-21 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1976, April 20-21 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1976, September 14 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, September 14 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, September 14 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Grievance Hearings Meeting, 1976, September 13 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Committee Meeting, 1976, September 14 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, September 14 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, September 14 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1976, September 15 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Multi-Conference Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 3], 1976, September 16-17 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Multi-Conference Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 3], 1976, September 16-17 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Multi-Conference Change of Operations Meeting [3 of 3], 1976, September 16-17 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1976, December 13 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1976, December 14 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1976, December 14 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting, 1976, December 14 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, December 14 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, December 14 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1976, December 15 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1976, December 15 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Council Meeting, 1977, March 21 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1977, March 22 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1977, March 22 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1977, March 22 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1977, March 22-23 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1977, March 22-23 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Yellow Freight System Meeting, 1977, June (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Freight Division Committee Meeting, 1977, June 13 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1977, June 14 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1977, June 14-15 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1977, June 14-15 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1977, June 14-15 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1977, June 15 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Joint Council Meeting, 1977, September 12 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1977, September 13 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1977, September 13-14 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1977, September 13-14 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1977, September 13-14 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1977, September 13-14 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1977, September 21 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1977, December 12 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1977, December 13 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1977, December 13 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1977, December 13-14 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1977, December 13-14 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Air Conditioning Committee Meeting, 1978, February 28 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Council Meeting, 1978, March 13 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1978, March 14 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1978, March 14-15 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1978, March 14-15 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1978, March 14-15 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1978, March 14-15 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Air Conditioning Committee Meeting, 1978, May 31 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1978, June 12 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1978, June 13 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1978, June 13 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1978, June 13-14 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1978, June 13-14 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1978, June 13-14 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Joint Air Conditioning Committee Meeting, 1978, August 30 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1978, September 11 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1978, September 12 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1978, September 12 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1978, September 12-13 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1978, September 12-13 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1978, September 12-13 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Special Hearing, 1978, October 27 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1978, December 11 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1978, December 12 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1978, December 12 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1978, December 12-13 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1978, December 12-13 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1978, December 12-13 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, January 11 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, January 11 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1979, June 11 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, June 12 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, June 12 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1979, June 12 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Steel and Special Commodity Meeting, 1979, June 12-14 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1979, June 12-14 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1979, June 12-14 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1979, June 14 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Council Meeting, 1979, September 10 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1979, September 11 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, September 11 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, September 11 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, September 11-12 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, September 11-12 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, September 11-12 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, September 11-12 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1979, September 12 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Meeting, 1979, September 11-13 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Council Meeting, 1979, December 10 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1979, December 11 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1979, December 11 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, December 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, December 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1979, December 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1979, December 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1979, December 11-12 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Joint Industry Committee Meeting, 1979, December 12 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Council Meeting, 1980, March 10 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, March 11 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, March 11 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1980, March 11 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, March 11-12 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, March 11-12 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1980, March 11-12 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, March 11-12 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, March 11-12 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1980, March 12 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1980, June 9 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1980, June 10 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1980, June 10 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, June 10-11 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, June 10-11 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1980, June 10-11 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, June 10-11 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, June 10-11 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1980, June 11 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1980, September 8 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1980, September 9 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1980, September 9 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1980, September 9-10 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, September 9-10 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, September 9-10 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, September 9-10 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, September 9-10 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1980, December 8 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1980, December 9 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1980, December 9 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Comittee Meeting [1 of 2], 1980, December 9-10 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1980, December 9-10 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1980, December 9-10 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1980, December 9-10 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1980, December 10 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Deadlocked Case Meeting, 1980, December 10 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1981, February 12 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Freight Division Conference Meeting, 1981, March 9 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1981, March 10 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1981, March 10 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1981, March 10-11 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1981, March 10-11 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1981, March 10-11 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1981, March 10-11 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1981, March 10-12 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1981, March 19 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1981, March 19 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Special Meeting, 1981, July 22 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Special Meeting, 1981, July 22 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Freight Division Conference Meeting, 1981, September 14 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1981, September 15 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1981, September 15 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1981, September 15-16 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1981, September 15-16 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1981, September 15-17 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1981, September 15-17 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1981, September 15-17 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1981, September 15-17 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1981, September 16 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Conference Meeting, 1981, December 14 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1981, December 15 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1981, December 15-16 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1981, December 15-16 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1981, December 15-16 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1981, December 15-16 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Council Meeting, 1982, March 8 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1982, March 9 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, March 9-10 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1982, March 9-10 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1982, March 10 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1982, June 14 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1982, June 15 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1982, June 15 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1982, June 15-16 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Joint Steel and Commodity Meeting, 1982, June 15-16 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, June 15-16 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, June 15-16 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Rider Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, June 17 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Rider Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, June 17 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1982, August 18 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 3], 1982, August 18-19 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 3], 1982, August 18-19 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting [3 of 3], 1982, August 18-19 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1982, September 13 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1982, September 14 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1982, September 14-15 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1982, September 14-15 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1982, September 14-15 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1982, September 14-15 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1982, September 14-15 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, September 14-15 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, September 14-15 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Competitive Review Board Meeting, 1982, September 15 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1982, September 15 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1982, September 16 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1982, November 9-10 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1982, December 13 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1982, December 14-15 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, January 18 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, January 18 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Rider Committee Meeting, 1983, January 18-19 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1983, March 14 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1983, March 15 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1983, March 15-16 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, March 15-16 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, March 15-16 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1983, March 15-16 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1983, March 15-17 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, April 13 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, April 13 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Area Union Rider Committee Meeting, 1983, April 13-14 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, April 14 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1983, June 13 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1983, June 14 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1983, June 14 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, June 14-15 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, June 14-15 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1983, June 14-15 (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1983, June 14-15 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, June 14-15 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, June 14-15 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1983, September 12 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1983, September 13 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1983, September 13 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1983, September 13-14 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, September 13-14 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, September 13-14 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1983, September 13-14 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, September 27 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, September 27 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1983, September 28 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Union Rider Committee Meeting, 1983, September 28 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1983, December 12 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1983, December 12-14 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1983, December 13 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1983, December 13-14 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1983, December 13-14 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1983, December 13-14 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1983, December 13-14 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Subcommittee Hearing Meeting, 1984, January 4 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, January 18 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, February 17 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, February 17 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1984, March 12 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1984, March 12-14 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Steel and Special Commodity Meeting, 1984, March 13 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1984, March 13-14 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1984, March 13-14 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 3], 1984, March 13-14 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 3], 1984, March 13-14 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [3 of 3], 1984, March 13-14 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1984, March 14 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1984, June 11 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1984, June 12 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1984, June 12-13 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1984, June 12-13 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1984, June 12-13 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1984, June 12-14 (Box 125, Folder 8)